Guide to the Doris Duke American Indian oral history project audio recordings 1949-1972
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1427)
  Stories of: The Priest's Daughter and The Serpent, Mah-Sah-Ka Daughter of a Priest, The Hopis, The War God Racing Horses, and The Outcast.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1428)
  Stories of: The Outcast, The Woodcutter and his Grandmother, and The Parrot's Feather and The Priest's Son.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1429)
  Stories of: The Parrot's Feather and The Priest's Son, War Gods and The Monster, The Gambler, and The Kid Roping The Buffalo.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1430)
  Stories of: The Kid Roping The Buffalo, The Little Boy and His Grandmother, and The Woodcutter.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1431)
  Stories of: The Woodcutter, The Witch of Zuni, The Village of Kat-Che-Ba-Wah, and a story of Eastern Pueblo.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1432)
  Stories of: Eastern Pueblo, The Deer Hunter, Ah-Ha-U-Da and The Salt mother, and Cat-Che-Bah-Wah.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1433)
  Stories of: Cat-Che-Bah-Wah, The Village of E-De-Won-Nah, and a story of the Earthquake.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1434)
  Stories of: The Earthquake, Witch Craft In Zuni, Coo-Bish-Dah-Yah, Massie's Childhood, and the Earthquake in Towayalane Village.
- Massie (Zuni), 1966-1967; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1435)
  Stories of: The Hopi Village, The Mexican, The Antelope and a Race Horse, and Hum-Sah-Wah and The Priest's Daughter.
- Ute Women's Conference, 1967 March 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1436)
  Recorded by S. Lyman Tyler and J. Witherspoon.
- Harold Tucson (Zuni), 1967 December 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1437)
  Interviewed and Recorded by D. C. Hammond
- Odd Halseth, 1968 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1438)
  Lecture on General Archaeology; Zuni Chants and Legends.
  Recorded by the staff of The Museum of Northern Arizona.
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others (Shoshoni), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1439)
  The Gosiute Reservation, early reservation history, relations with soldiers, relations with Mormons, the story of The Indian God and the Creation of The World, Historical Ethnography, Antelope Shaman, Lincoln Highway, Chinese at Cherry Creek, early stores, and various early Native stories.
  Recorded for Shoshone Language Materials
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1440)
  Historical Ethnography.
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1441)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1442)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1443)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1444)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1445)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1446)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1447)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1448)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1449)
  Historical Ethnography, Owyhee Text and Owyhee School.
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1450)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1451)
  Historical Ethnography, Gosiute and Shoshoni Sentences.
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1452)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1453)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1454)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1455)
- Shoshone Language Materials: Maude Moon; Jack Simms, Edna Simms; Albert McGill; Eva Steele; Jack Guna; Mrs. Garcia; Minnie Bishop; Bessie Hall, and others, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1456)
- Recordings unavailable (Reel 1457-1459)
- N. Scott Momaday, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1460)
  Interviewed and Recorded by E. Bulow
- John Kitchen (Navajo), 1972 August 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1461)
  Recollections of The Navajo Long Walk.
- Doris Duke American Indian Oral History Promotional Tape, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1462)
  Five minute tape introduction to the American Indian Oral History Project with Nick Mills narrating. Quotes from: Lance Eagleman, Frank Timbinloo, Clyde Benally, Moroni Timbinloo, Lulu Brock, Oran Curry, and Frank Smith.
- Doris Duke American Indian Oral History Promotional Tape, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1463)
  Radio Program promotional containing splices from American Indian Oral History tapes. Narrated by Nick Mills.
  Running Time: 25 Min.
- Setan Clark, Charley Begay, Ashii Tsosie or "Slim Salt" (Navajo), 1970 August 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1464)
- Hettie Nepah, Hastiin Claw, Frank Lefty (Navajo), 1961 January 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1465)